

var questions=[{
    "question":" 1.What is the name of The Beatles first album?",
    "option1":" Please Please Me",
    "option2": "With the Beatles",
    "option3":"Help!",
    "option4":"All You Need Is Love",
    "answer":"1",
},
{ "question": "2.Which former One Direction member released Watermelon Sugar and Adore You?",
"option1":"Harry Styles",
"option2":"Zayn",
"option3":"Niall Horan",
"option4":"Liam Payne",
"answer":"1",

},
{ "question":"3.Which female artist released the single Rolling in the Deep? ",
"option1":"Celine Dion",
"option2":"Adele",
"option3":"Ariana Grande",
"option4":"Nicky Minaj",
"answer":"2",
},{
    "question":"4.Which band recorded the theme song to Friends?",
    "option1":"SteelHeart",
    "option2":"One Direction",
    "option3":"ColdPlay",
    "option4":" The Rembrandts",
    "answer":"4",
},{
    "question":" 5.Which American rock band had a hit in the eighties with the Eye of the Tiger?",
    "option1":"Dynatzy",
    "option2":"The Beatles",
    "option3":"Survivor",
    "option4":"AC/DC",
    "answer":"3",
},{
    "question":" 6.What was the name of Eminem's first UK single release in 1999?",
    "option1":"My Name Is",
    "option2":"Not Afraid",
    "option3":"Mockingbird",
    "option4":"When Im Gone",
    "answer":"1",
},{
    "question":"7.Which singer has the most Twitter followers?",
    "option1":"Justin Bieber",
    "option2":"Taylor Swift",
    "option3":"Lady Gaga",
    "option4":"Eminem",
    "answer":"1",
},{
    "question":"8.According to the lyrics of Kelis Milkshake , released in 2003, where does her milkshake bring all the boys?",
    "option1":"To The House",
    "option2":"To The Club",
    "option3":"To The Party",
    "option4":"To The Yard",
    "answer":"4",
},{
    "question":"9.Which mathematical symbol was the title of Ed Sheerans first album in 2011?",
    "option1":" - ",
    "option2":" + ",
    "option3":" * ",
    "option4":" $ ",
    "answer":"2",
},{
    "question":" 10.In a 2011 single, Maroon 5 claimed to have moves like which member of the Rolling Stones?",
    "option1":"Carlo Little",
    "option2":"Brian Jones",
    "option3":"Mick Taylor",
    "option4":"Mick Jagger",
    "answer":"4",
}

]